const allQuestions = [{
      "question": "What did the duck say when he bought lipstick?",
      "correct": "Put it on my bill.",
      "answers": ["False", "True"]
   }, {  
      "question": "How do you count cows?",
      "correct": "With a cowculator.",
      "answers": ["False", "True"]
   },
   {  
      "question": "Can a kangaroo jump higher than the Empire State Building?",
      "correct": "Of course. The Empire State Building can't jump.",
      "answers": ["False", "True"]
   },
   {  
      "question": "Why did the chicken cross the playground?",
      "correct": "To get to the other slide!!",
      "answers": ["False", "True"]
   },
   {  
      "question": "What's the difference between a cat and a complex sentence?",
      "correct": "A cat has claws at the end of its paws and a complex sentence has a pause at the end of its clause.",
      "answers": ["False", "True"]
   },
   {  
      "question": "Why did the turkey cross the road?",
      "correct": "Because he wasn't a chicken.",
      "answers": ["False", "True"]
   },
   {  
      "question": "What do you call a rabbit that has fleas?",
      "correct": "Bugs bunny.",
      "answers": ["False", "True"]
   },
   {  
      "question": "Why did the dinosaur cross the road?",
      "correct": "Chickens didn't exist yet.",
      "answers": ["False", "True"]
   },
   {  
      "question": "Why is the barn so noisy?",
      "correct": "Because the cows have horns.",
      "answers": ["False", "True"]
   },
   {  
      "question": "How do you make a tissue dance?",
      "correct": "Put a little boogie in it.",
      "answers": ["False", "True"]
   },
   {  
      "question": "What’s the best thing about Switzerland?",
      "correct": "I don't know, but the flag is a big plus.",
      "answers": ["False", "True"]
   },
   {  
      "question": "Why are there no knock knock jokes about America?",
      "correct": "Because freedom rings!",
      "answers": ["False", "True"]
   },
   {  
      "question": "Why do the French eat snails?",
      "correct": "They don't like fast food.",
      "answers": ["False", "True"]
   },
   {  
      "question": "Which state has the most questions?",
      "correct": "Alaska.",
      "answers": ["False", "True"]
   },
   {  
      "question": "How did I get to Iraq?",
      "correct": "Iran.",
      "answers": ["False", "True"]
   },
   {  
      "question": "If a plane crashed on the Canada/USA border, where would the survivors be buried?",
      "correct": "You don't bury survivors.",
      "answers": ["False", "True"]
   },
   {  
      "question": "How do astronomers organize a party?",
      "correct": "They planet.",
      "answers": ["False", "True"]
   },
   {  
      "question": "Why did the chicken cross the möbius strip?",
      "correct": "To get to the same side.",
      "answers": ["False", "True"]
   },
   {  
      "question": "Why are Helium, Curium, and Barium the medical elements? ",
      "correct": "Because if you can't heal-ium or cure-ium, you bury-um.",
      "answers": ["False", "True"]
   },
   {  
      "question": "Why do centipedes have 100 legs?",
      "correct": "So they can walk.",
      "answers": ["False", "True"]
   },
   {  
      "question": "Why can't you trust an atom?",
      "correct": "Because they make up everything.",
      "answers": ["False", "True"]
   },
   {  
      "question": "What did the 30 degree angle say to the 90 degree angle?",
      "correct": "You think you're always right!",
      "answers": ["False", "True"]
   },
   {  
      "question": "Why did the golfer wear two pairs of pants?",
      "correct": "In case he got a hole in one.",
      "answers": ["False", "True"]
   },
   {  
      "question": "Why did the coach go back to the bank?",
      "correct": "To get his quarterback!",
      "answers": ["False", "True"]
   },
   {  
      "question": "Why is a baseball game a good place to go on a hot day?",
      "correct": "Because there are lots of fans.",
      "answers": ["False", "True"]
   },
   {  
      "question": "Which sport is always in trouble?",
      "correct": "BADminton.",
      "answers": ["False", "True"]
   },
   {  
      "question": "Why did the cookie go to the doctor's office?",
      "correct": "It was feeling crummy.",
      "answers": ["False", "True"]
   },
   {  
      "question": "How do you know that carrots are good for your eyesight?",
      "correct": "Have you ever seen a rabbit with glasses?",
      "answers": ["False", "True"]
   },
   {  
      "question": "Why'd the robber take a bath?",
      "correct": "He wanted to make a clean getaway.",
      "answers": ["False", "True"]
   },
   {  
      "question": "Which part of the military do babies join?",
      "correct": "The infantry.",
      "answers": ["False", "True"]
   },
   {  
      "question": "What starts with a P, ends with an E, and has a 1,000 letters?",
      "correct": "Post office.",
      "answers": ["False", "True"]
   },
   {  
      "question": "Why are ghosts bad liars?",
      "correct": "You can see right through them.",
      "answers": ["False", "True"]
   },
   {  
      "question": "What's the difference between a guitar and a fish?",
      "correct": "You can tune a guitar, but you can't tuna fish.",
      "answers": ["False", "True"]
   },
   {  
      "question": "What do you call a woman that sets her bills on fire?",
      "correct": "Bernadette",
      "answers": ["False", "True"]
   },
   {  
      "question": "What does a skeleton order at a restaurant?",
      "correct": "Spare ribs!",
      "answers": ["False", "True"]
   },
   {  
      "question": "What happens once in a minute and twice in a moment but never in a decade?",
      "correct": "The letter m",
      "answers": ["False", "True"]
   },
   {  
      "question": "What type of sandals do frogs wear?",
      "correct": "Open-toad!",
      "answers": ["False", "True"]
   },
   {  
      "question": "Why did the fish blush?",
      "correct": "Because it saw the ocean's bottom.",
      "answers": ["False", "True"]
   },
   {  
      "question": "How many politicians does it take to change a light bulb?",
      "correct": "Two: one to change it and another one to change it back again.",
      "answers": ["False", "True"]
   },
   {  
      "question": "How come oysters never donate to charity?",
      "correct": "Because they are shellfish.",
      "answers": ["False", "True"]
   },
   {  
      "question": "What kind of key opens a banana?",
      "correct": "A monkey.",
      "answers": ["False", "True"]
   },
   {  
      "question": "What did the grape say when it was stepped on?",
      "correct": "Nothing, it just let out a little wine.",
      "answers": ["False", "True"]
   },
   {  
      "question": "What do you call a cow with two legs?",
      "correct": "Lean beef.",
      "answers": ["False", "True"]
   },
   {  
      "question": "Why did the tofu cross the road?",
      "correct": "To prove it wasn't chicken.",
      "answers": ["False", "True"]
   },
   {  
      "question": "What do you get from a pampered cow?",
      "correct": "Spoiled milk.",
      "answers": ["False", "True"]
   },
   {  
      "question": "Why can't you tell an egg a joke?",
      "correct": "Because it will crack up.",
      "answers": ["False", "True"]
   },
   {  
      "question": "How can you drop a raw egg onto a concrete floor without cracking it?",
      "correct": "Any way you want, concrete floors are very hard to crack.",
      "answers": ["False", "True"]
   },
   {  
      "question": "How do you turn white chocolate into dark chocolate?",
      "correct": "Turn off the light.",
      "answers": ["False", "True"]
   },
   {  
      "question": "What did Obi-Wan say to Luke at the breakfast table?",
      "correct": "Use the fork, Luke.",
      "answers": ["False", "True"]
   },
   {  
      "question": "Did you hear about the cat that drank 5 bowls of water?",
      "correct": " He set a new lap record.",
      "answers": ["False", "True"]
   },
   {  
      "question": "How can you stop a skunk from smelling?",
      "correct": " Hold its nose shut.",
      "answers": ["False", "True"]
   },
   {  
      "question": "How do cats buy things?",
      "correct": " From a cat-alogue!",
      "answers": ["False", "True"]
   },
   {  
      "question": "How do you keep a dog from barking in your front yard?",
      "correct": " Put him in your back yard.",
      "answers": ["False", "True"]
   },
   {  
      "question": "How do you keep someone in suspense?",
      "correct": "I'll tell you tomorrow.",
      "answers": ["False", "True"]
   },
   {  
      "question": "How do you make gold soup?",
      "correct": " Put 14 carrots in it.",
      "answers": ["False", "True"]
   },
   {  
      "question": "How do you stop a charging rhinoceros?",
      "correct": " Take away his credit cards.",
      "answers": ["False", "True"]
   },
   {  
      "question": "How does a cat sing scales?",
      "correct": " Do-ri-me-ow!",
      "answers": ["False", "True"]
   },
   {  
      "question": "How does a ghost start a letter?",
      "correct": " Tomb it may concern.",
      "answers": ["False", "True"]
   },
   {  
      "question": "How does a group of dolphins make a decision?",
      "correct": " Flipper coin.",
      "answers": ["False", "True"]
   },
   {  
      "question": "How does the cat get its own way?",
      "correct": " With friendly purrsuasion.",
      "answers": ["False", "True"]
   },
   {  
      "question": "How is cat food sold?",
      "correct": " Usually purr-can.",
      "answers": ["False", "True"]
   },
   {  
      "question": "How many months have 28 days?",
      "correct": " All of them.",
      "answers": ["False", "True"]
   },
   {  
      "question": "How much does it cost a pirate to get their ears pierced?",
      "correct": " A Buc-an-ear.",
      "answers": ["False", "True"]
   },
   {  
      "question": "If a cat can jump five feet high then why can't it jump through a three foot window?",
      "correct": " Because the window is closed.",
      "answers": ["False", "True"]
   },
   {  
      "question": "If an apple a day keeps the doctor away what does an onion do?",
      "correct": " Keeps everyone away.",
      "answers": ["False", "True"]
   },
   {  
      "question": "If two's company and three a crowd what's four and five?",
      "correct": " Nine.",
      "answers": ["False", "True"]
   },
   {  
      "question": "To whom do fish go to borrow money?",
      "correct": " The loan shark.",
      "answers": ["False", "True"]
   },
   {  
      "question": "Two flies are on the porch. Which one is the actor?",
      "correct": " The one on the screen.",
      "answers": ["False", "True"]
   },
   {  
      "question": "Two silk worms were in a race. What was the result?",
      "correct": " A tie.",
      "answers": ["False", "True"]
   },
   {  
      "question": "What animal needs oil?",
      "correct": " The mouse, because it squeaks.",
      "answers": ["False", "True"]
   },
   {  
      "question": "What animals are on legal documents?",
      "correct": " Seals.",
      "answers": ["False", "True"]
   },
   {  
      "question": "What bird is always out of breath?",
      "correct": " A puffin.",
      "answers": ["False", "True"]
   },
   {  
      "question": "What bird steals from the rich to give to the poor?",
      "correct": " Robin Hood.",
      "answers": ["False", "True"]
   },
   {  
      "question": "What birds spend all their time on their knees?",
      "correct": " Birds of prey.",
      "answers": ["False", "True"]
   },
   {  
      "question": "What did one eye say to the other?",
      "correct": " Between you and me, something smells.",
      "answers": ["False", "True"]
   },
   {  
      "question": "What did one math book say to the other?",
      "correct": " Man, I got a lot of problems.",
      "answers": ["False", "True"]
   },
   {  
      "question": "What did one plate say to the other plate?",
      "correct": " Lunch is on me.",
      "answers": ["False", "True"]
   },
   {  
      "question": "What did one tube of glue say to the other tube of glue?",
      "correct": " We have to stick together.",
      "answers": ["False", "True"]
   },
   {  
      "question": "What did the cat say when he lost all his money?",
      "correct": " I'm paw!",
      "answers": ["False", "True"]
   },
   {  
      "question": "What did the confused bee say?",
      "correct": " To bee or not to bee.",
      "answers": ["False", "True"]
   },
   {  
      "question": "What did the digital clock say to his mother?",
      "correct": " Look Mom, no hands!",
      "answers": ["False", "True"]
   },
   {  
      "question": "What did the dog say when it sat on sandpaper?",
      "correct": " Ruff!",
      "answers": ["False", "True"]
   },
   {  
      "question": "What did the football coach say to the broken vending machine?",
      "correct": " Give me my quarterback!",
      "answers": ["False", "True"]
   },
   {  
      "question": "What did the mountain climber name his son?",
      "correct": " Cliff.",
      "answers": ["False", "True"]
   },
   {  
      "question": "What did the painter say to the wall?",
      "correct": " One more crack, and I'll plaster you.",
      "answers": ["False", "True"]
   },
   {  
      "question": "What did the picture say to the other picture?",
      "correct": " I heard you got framed.",
      "answers": ["False", "True"]
   },
   {  
      "question": "What did the picture say to the wall?",
      "correct": " I've got you covered.",
      "answers": ["False", "True"]
   },
   {  
      "question": "What did the right shoe say to the left shoe?",
      "correct": " I think we must be sole mates.",
      "answers": ["False", "True"]
   },
   {  
      "question": "What did the silly comedian bake on his day off?",
      "correct": " Cornbread.",
      "answers": ["False", "True"]
   },
   {  
      "question": "What did the snake say when another asked him the time?",
      "correct": " Don't asp me.",
      "answers": ["False", "True"]
   },
   {  
      "question": "What did the talking hat say to the scarf?",
      "correct": " You can hang around. I'll just go on ahead.",
      "answers": ["False", "True"]
   },
   {  
      "question": "What did the termite say when he entered the bar?",
      "correct": " Is the bar tender here?",
      "answers": ["False", "True"]
   },
   {  
      "question": "What did the toilet say to the other toilet?",
      "correct": " You look a little flushed.",
      "answers": ["False", "True"]
   },
   {  
      "question": "What do cat actors say on stage ?",
      "correct": " Tabby or not tabby!",
      "answers": ["False", "True"]
   },
   {  
      "question": "What do cats use to make coffee?",
      "correct": " A purrcolator.",
      "answers": ["False", "True"]
   },
   {  
      "question": "What do elves do after school?",
      "correct": " Gnomework.",
      "answers": ["False", "True"]
   },
   {  
      "question": "What do frogs eat with their hamburgers?",
      "correct": " French flies.",
      "answers": ["False", "True"]
   },
   {  
      "question": "What do people in prison use to communicate with one another?",
      "correct": " Cell phones.",
      "answers": ["False", "True"]
   },
   {  
      "question": "What do pigs put on their sore toes?",
      "correct": " Oinkment.",
      "answers": ["False", "True"]
   },
   {  
      "question": "What do porcupines say after they kiss?",
      "correct": " Ouch!",
      "answers": ["False", "True"]
   },
   {  
      "question": "What do skeletons say before a meal?",
      "correct": " Bone appetite.",
      "answers": ["False", "True"]
   },
   {  
      "question": "What do you call a boomerang that doesn't work?",
      "correct": " A stick.",
      "answers": ["False", "True"]
   },
   {  
      "question": "What do you call a cow in an earthquake?",
      "correct": " A milkshake.",
      "answers": ["False", "True"]
   },
   {  
      "question": "What do you call a deer with no eyes?",
      "correct": " No eye-deer.",
      "answers": ["False", "True"]
   },
   {  
      "question": "What do you call a dentist in the Army?",
      "correct": " A drill sergeant.",
      "answers": ["False", "True"]
   },
   {  
      "question": "What do you call a donkey with ear muffs on?",
      "correct": " Anything you want. He can't hear you.",
      "answers": ["False", "True"]
   },
   {  
      "question": "What do you call a fish with no eyes?",
      "correct": " A fsh.",
      "answers": ["False", "True"]
   },
   {  
      "question": "What do you call a fly that doesn't have any wings?",
      "correct": " A walk.",
      "answers": ["False", "True"]
   },
   {  
      "question": "What do you call a man who doesn't sink?",
      "correct": " Bob.",
      "answers": ["False", "True"]
   },
   {  
      "question": "What do you call a rude bird?",
      "correct": " A mockingbird.",
      "answers": ["False", "True"]
   },
   {  
      "question": "What do you call a scared dinosaur?",
      "correct": " A nervous Rex.",
      "answers": ["False", "True"]
   },
   {  
      "question": "What do you call a shoe made from a banana?",
      "correct": " A Slipper.",
      "answers": ["False", "True"]
   },
   {  
      "question": "What do you call a sleeping cow?",
      "correct": " A bulldozer.",
      "answers": ["False", "True"]
   },
   {  
      "question": "What do you call a snake that works for the government?",
      "correct": " A civil serpent.",
      "answers": ["False", "True"]
   },
   {  
      "question": "What do you call it when a cat bites?",
      "correct": " Catnip!",
      "answers": ["False", "True"]
   },
   {  
      "question": "What do you call it when a cat stops?",
      "correct": " A paws.",
      "answers": ["False", "True"]
   },
   {  
      "question": "What do you find at the end of everything?",
      "correct": " The letter g.",
      "answers": ["False", "True"]
   },
   {  
      "question": "What do you get when mixing a tiger and a snowman?",
      "correct": " Frost Bite.",
      "answers": ["False", "True"]
   },
   {  
      "question": "What do you get when two giraffes collide?",
      "correct": " A giraffic jam.",
      "answers": ["False", "True"]
   },
   {  
      "question": "What do you get when you cross a cat with a lemon?",
      "correct": " A sourpuss.",
      "answers": ["False", "True"]
   },
   {  
      "question": "What do you say to the skeleton going on vacation?",
      "correct": " Bone voyage.",
      "answers": ["False", "True"]
   },
   {  
      "question": "What do you use to comb a cat?",
      "correct": " A catacomb.",
      "answers": ["False", "True"]
   },
   {  
      "question": "What does a cell phone give his girlfriend?",
      "correct": " A ring.",
      "answers": ["False", "True"]
   },
   {  
      "question": "What does an envelope say when you lick it?",
      "correct": " Nothing. It just shuts up.",
      "answers": ["False", "True"]
   },
   {  
      "question": "What does an octopus wear in the winter?",
      "correct": " A coat of arms.",
      "answers": ["False", "True"]
   },
   {  
      "question": "What does the ocean say to the boat?",
      "correct": " Nothing. It just waves.",
      "answers": ["False", "True"]
   },
   {  
      "question": "What dog loves to take bubble baths?",
      "correct": " A shampoodle.",
      "answers": ["False", "True"]
   },
   {  
      "question": "What followed the dinosaur?",
      "correct": " Its tail.",
      "answers": ["False", "True"]
   },
   {  
      "question": "What food can make you rich?",
      "correct": " Fortune cookies.",
      "answers": ["False", "True"]
   },
   {  
      "question": "What happened when the wheel was invented?",
      "correct": " It caused a revolution.",
      "answers": ["False", "True"]
   },
   {  
      "question": "What has four wheels no wings and flies?",
      "correct": " A garbage truck.",
      "answers": ["False", "True"]
   },
   {  
      "question": "What has lots of teeth but cannot chew?",
      "correct": " A comb.",
      "answers": ["False", "True"]
   },
   {  
      "question": "What has more lives than a cat?",
      "correct": " A frog, because it croaks every night.",
      "answers": ["False", "True"]
   },
   {  
      "question": "What is black and white and pink all over?",
      "correct": " An embarrassed zebra.",
      "answers": ["False", "True"]
   },
   {  
      "question": "What is full of holes but can still hold water?",
      "correct": " A sponge.",
      "answers": ["False", "True"]
   },
   {  
      "question": "What is it that even the most careful person overlooks?",
      "correct": " His nose.",
      "answers": ["False", "True"]
   },
   {  
      "question": "What is taller when it sits down than when it stands up?",
      "correct": " A dog.",
      "answers": ["False", "True"]
   },
   {  
      "question": "What is Tarzan's favorite Christmas song?",
      "correct": " Jungle Bells.",
      "answers": ["False", "True"]
   },
   {  
      "question": "What is the difference between a well-dressed man and a dog?",
      "correct": " The man wears a suit, the dog just pants.",
      "answers": ["False", "True"]
   },
   {  
      "question": "What is the most slippery country in the world?",
      "correct": " Greece.",
      "answers": ["False", "True"]
   },
   {  
      "question": "What jam can't be eaten on toast?",
      "correct": " A traffic jam.",
      "answers": ["False", "True"]
   },
   {  
      "question": "What kind of dog tells time?",
      "correct": " A watch dog.",
      "answers": ["False", "True"]
   },
   {  
      "question": "What kind of horses go out after dark?",
      "correct": " Nightmares.",
      "answers": ["False", "True"]
   },
   {  
      "question": "What kind of keys do kids like to carry?",
      "correct": " Cookies.",
      "answers": ["False", "True"]
   },
   {  
      "question": "What kind of rooms have no walls?",
      "correct": " Mushrooms.",
      "answers": ["False", "True"]
   },
   {  
      "question": "What lies at the bottom of the ocean and twitches?",
      "correct": " A nervous wreck.",
      "answers": ["False", "True"]
   },
   {  
      "question": "What mouse was a Roman emperor?",
      "correct": " Julius Cheeser.",
      "answers": ["False", "True"]
   },
   {  
      "question": "What never gets any wetter no matter how much it rains?",
      "correct": " The sea.",
      "answers": ["False", "True"]
   },
   {  
      "question": "What pet makes the loudest noise?",
      "correct": " A trum-pet.",
      "answers": ["False", "True"]
   },
   {  
      "question": "What runs but never walks?",
      "correct": " Water.",
      "answers": ["False", "True"]
   },
   {  
      "question": "What side of the cat has the most fur?",
      "correct": " The OUT-side.",
      "answers": ["False", "True"]
   },
   {  
      "question": "What snakes are good at sums?",
      "correct": " Adders.",
      "answers": ["False", "True"]
   },
   {  
      "question": "What sport do cats play?",
      "correct": " Hairball.",
      "answers": ["False", "True"]
   },
   {  
      "question": "What stories do the ship captain's children like to hear?",
      "correct": " Ferry tales.",
      "answers": ["False", "True"]
   },
   {  
      "question": "What time is it when an elephant sits on a fence?",
      "correct": " Time to get a new fence.",
      "answers": ["False", "True"]
   },
   {  
      "question": "What time is it when seven cats are chasing a mouse?",
      "correct": " Seven after one.",
      "answers": ["False", "True"]
   },
   {  
      "question": "What type of bow can never be tied?",
      "correct": " A Rainbow.",
      "answers": ["False", "True"]
   },
   {  
      "question": "What vegetable needs a plumber?",
      "correct": " A leek.",
      "answers": ["False", "True"]
   },
   {  
      "question": "What would you get if you crossed a pig with a karate expert?",
      "correct": " Pork chops.",
      "answers": ["False", "True"]
   },
   {  
      "question": "What's an insect's favorite sport?",
      "correct": " Cricket.",
      "answers": ["False", "True"]
   },
   {  
      "question": "What's happening when you hear woof... splat... meow... splat?",
      "correct": " It's raining cats and dogs.",
      "answers": ["False", "True"]
   },
   {  
      "question": "When a dirty kid has finished taking a bath what is still dirty?",
      "correct": " The bathtub.",
      "answers": ["False", "True"]
   },
   {  
      "question": "When does Friday come before Thursday?",
      "correct": " In the dictionary.",
      "answers": ["False", "True"]
   },
   {  
      "question": "When is a baseball player like a thief?",
      "correct": " When he steals a base.",
      "answers": ["False", "True"]
   },
   {  
      "question": "When is a car not a car?",
      "correct": " When it turns into a garage.",
      "answers": ["False", "True"]
   },
   {  
      "question": "When is a door not a door?",
      "correct": " When it's ajar.",
      "answers": ["False", "True"]
   },
   {  
      "question": "When is it unlucky to see a black cat?",
      "correct": " When you're a mouse.",
      "answers": ["False", "True"]
   },
   {  
      "question": "Where can you find an ocean with no water?",
      "correct": " On a map.",
      "answers": ["False", "True"]
   },
   {  
      "question": "Where did the fortune teller go on her vacation?",
      "correct": " Palm Beach.",
      "answers": ["False", "True"]
   },
   {  
      "question": "Why was the banker bored?",
      "correct": " Because he lost interest in everything.",
      "answers": ["False", "True"]
   },
   {  
      "question": "Why was 6 afraid of 7?",
      "correct": " Because 7-8-9.",
      "answers": ["False", "True"]
   },   
   {  
      "question": "Why is the bride always out of luck on her wedding day?",
      "correct": " Because she never marries the best man.",
      "answers": ["False", "True"]
   },
   {  
      "question": "Why is it so hard for a leopard to hide?",
      "correct": " Because he's always spotted.",
      "answers": ["False", "True"]
   },
      {  
      "question": "Why do you always find the cat in the last place you look?",
      "correct": " Because you stop looking after you find it.",
      "answers": ["False", "True"]
   },
   {  
      "question": "Why do hens lay eggs?",
      "correct": "If they drop them, they would break.",
      "answers": ["False", "True"]
   },
   {  
      "question": "Why do Hummingbirds hum?",
      "correct": " They've never learned the words.",
      "answers": ["False", "True"]
   },
   {  
      "question": "Why do people go to bed?",
      "correct": "Because the bed won't come to them.",
      "answers": ["False", "True"]
   },



{
  "question": "If there are three pineapples and you take two, how many will you have?",
  "correct": "2",
  "answers": ["2", "1", "0", "3"]
}, {
  "question": "A mother has 6 daughters and each of them has a brother. How many children are there?",
  "correct": "7",
  "answers": ["6", "7", "12", "10"]
}, {
  "question": "Charlie asked Margaret how old she was and she answered him: In two years I will be twice as old as I was five years ago. How old is she?",
  "correct": "12",
  "answers": ["12", "6", "7", "24"]
}, {
  "question": "The stubs obtained by burning ten candles will yield one extra candle if you melt them all together. If you burned 100 candles, how many extra candles could you make?",
  "correct": "11",
  "answers": ["11", "8", "9", "10"]
}, {
  "question": "A fish costs a dollar and half a fish. How much do 5 fish cost?",
  "correct": "$10",
  "answers": ["$20", "$10", "$15", "$5"]
}, {
  "question": "There are 15 birds sitting on the branches of a tree. A hunter goes by and shoots 3 of them. How many birds are left on the tree?",
  "correct": "0",
  "answers": ["12", "10", "3", "0"]
}, {
  "question": "What number multiplied by 10 equals the square of the same number, times 5?",
  "correct": "2",
  "answers": ["4", "5", "2", "10"]
}, {
  "question": "Five years ago the sum of the age of a sister and a brother was 8. What will be the same sum in 5 years?",
  "correct": "28",
  "answers": ["It will not change.", "18", "13", "28"]
}, {
  "question": "If I had $654,987, how much change is that?",
  "correct": "65,498,700 cents",
  "answers": ["66,345,200 cents", "65,783,500 cents", "65,498,700 cents", "65,577,200 cents"]
}, {
  "question": "A monster had double the amount of eyes he had ears, triple the amount of ears he had legs, and had six legs. How many eyes did he have?",
  "correct": "36",
  "answers": ["34", "26", "36", "41"]
}, {
  "question": "There is a branch with 10 birds on it. I shot 2 of them and then 1 more. How many birds are left on the branch?",
  "correct": "0",
  "answers": ["0", "2", "8", "7"]
}, {
  "question": "If you have in your suitcase 6 white socks, 4 red socks, 8 green socks, and 2 brown socks, how many socks would you have to pull out (without looking at them) to be sure you have a matching pair?",
  "correct": "5",
  "answers": ["6", "8", "4", "5"]
}, {
  "question": "Joe had 29 pairs of socks. How many socks did he have?",
  "correct": "58",
  "answers": ["60", "58", "56", "29"]
}, {
  "question": "One camera could take 350 pictures and Bob bought 3 cameras of the same type. How many pictures could he take?",
  "correct": "1050",
  "answers": ["700", "none", "1050", "350"]
}, {
  "question": "One iPod can hold 950 songs and 3 movies. How many iPods of this model would one person have to buy to have 27 movies and 8550 songs?",
  "correct": "9",
  "answers": ["8", "10", "7", "9"]
}, {
  "question": "In an office building, there are 350 windows and half as many doors. How many doors are there in 3 office buildings?",
  "correct": "525",
  "answers": ["525", "500", "550", "575"]
}, {
  "question": "The vegetable rhubarb is delicious but its leaves are poisonous. What did rhubarb originally mean?",
  "correct": "root of the barbarian",
  "answers": ["edible poison", "beware", "root of the barbarian", "poisoned ruby"]
}, {
  "question": "What modern slang term once meant a carnival worker who performed disgusting tasks such as biting off the heads of live chickens?",
  "correct": "Geek",
  "answers": ["Nerd", "Geek", "Dork", "Freak"]
}, {
  "question": "What is heavier a pound of bricks or a pound of feathers?",
  "correct": "Their weight is equal",
  "answers": ["There is no way to tell", "The feathers", "Their weight is equal", "The bricks"]
}, {
  "question": "Which is the month that allows women to talk the least?",
  "correct": "February",
  "answers": ["February", "December", "August", "March"]
}, {
  "question": "What creature is responsible for the most human deaths?",
  "correct": "The mosquito",
  "answers": ["The brown recluse spider", "The hippo", "The great white shark", "The mosquito"]
}, {
  "question": "Take two apples from three apples and what do you have?",
  "correct": "two apples",
  "answers": ["no apples", "two apples", "three apples", "one apple"]
}, {
  "question": "12 candles were alight. The wind blew out 5 of them. How many candles were left?",
  "correct": "12",
  "answers": ["0", "7", "12", "5"]
},


{
  "question": "Clouds are made up of these.",
  "correct": "Water droplets and ice crystals",
  "answers": ["Carbon atoms", "Water droplets and ice crystals", "Oxygen ions", "Dust mites"]
}, {
  "question": "It is the only continent that does not have land areas below sea level.",
  "correct": "Antarctica",
  "answers": ["Australia", "South America", "Antarctica", "Arctica"]
}, {
  "question": "This is a gemstone made by fossilized tree sap that is at least 30 million years old.",
  "correct": "Amber",
  "answers": ["Obsidian", "Amber", "Tourmaline", "Malachite"]
}, {
  "question": "This is the largest island on Earth and one third of it is a national park.",
  "correct": "Greenland",
  "answers": ["Greenland", "Madagaskar", "Australia", "Alaska"]
}, {
  "question": "Which organ has no known function in the human body?",
  "correct": "appendix",
  "answers": ["tonsils", "appendix", "uvula", "pineal gland"]
}, {
  "question": "This planet is slightly smaller than Earth and its closest neighbor (excluding the Moon).",
  "correct": "Venus",
  "answers": ["Venus", "Uranus", "Mars", "Saturn"]
}, {
  "question": "Which Solar System celestial bodys revolution around the Sun takes 248 years?",
  "correct": "Pluto",
  "answers": ["Saturn", "Pluto", "Neptune", "Uranus"]
}, {
  "question": "Chop Suey, a pasta dish consisting of short noodles, was originally made and served in which country?",
  "correct": "USA",
  "answers": ["Thailand", "USA", "China", "Vietnam"]
}, {
  "question": "Your physician has ordered an electroencephalogram (EEG), the graphic recording of the electrical activity of what organ?",
  "correct": "Brain",
  "answers": ["Muscles", "Liver", "Heart", "Brain"]
}];